# Reshef Kama

# Full Stack Developer

# **My Contact**

🕍 reshef.ka@gmail.com



972-544818405



www.linkedin.com/in/reshef-kama



https://reshefk.github.io/Reshef.portfolio/#



https://github.com/ReshefK

# **Education Background**

## **JHON BRYCE**

Certificate Full Stack Development Completed in 2021

# **University of Haifa**

MA International Relations Completed in 2013

## **College of Management**

**BA Behavioral Sciences** Completed in 2007

# Skill

- Java Spring, Spring boot, Java EE, Hibernate/JPA
- HTML 5, CSS, JSON, JQuery, Java Script, SpringMVC, React.
- · SPRING. Cloud, Microservices.

# **About Me**

Dedicated and efficient full stuck developer, passion for developing scalable web application and working across the

Certified in both F/E and B/E technologies. Extensive experience in management and production. Ability and efficiency at coordinating and synchronizing interfaces.

Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities.

# **Professional Experience**

## EL-AL IT Division | Java Full Stack Developer

2022 - Present

#### **Key responsibilities:**

- Consulted with engineering team members to determine system loads and develop improvement plans.
- Design, implement and test code to deliver business solutions focus on best user experience, performance, security and future expansion.
- Developed clear specifications for project plans using customer requirements.
- Used NodeJS, ORM and MY-SQL to develop and manage databases.
- Performs necessary quality assurance activities to ensure code performs as defined by business requirements.

## El-Al Cargo | Deputy Manager Import Department

2015 - 2022

#### **Key responsibilities:**

- Managing Operations / Service Team and performance control of air import shipments.
- Prioritizing and routing; according to constraints, while providing professional guidance.
- Development and application of protocol service and operations in Israel and abroad (HUB).
- Development of work schemes with various interfaces in the company catalyzing maximize trade and services.
- Managing business with various interfaces, customs / trade / security / procurement in Israel and abroad.
- Professional authority with all company interfaces for the benefit of promoting tasks and project.

# **EI-AL Operation | Operations Officer**

2013 - 2015

#### **Key responsibilities:**

- Provided excellent customer care to maintain and improve customer relations, increase product and service sales.
- Control of the operational activities in the passenger and cargo area at Ben Gurion Airport.
- · Coordination between many operational interfaces, including EL AL's stations abroad.
- · Adherence to schedules and operational accuracy in terms of activity in the aircraft area.
- Provide solutions in solving problems that combine high technical and safety capabilities.